You're never too small to dream big.
GOAT is a animation, comedy, family film directed by Tyree Dillihay.
Will, a small goat with big dreams, gets a once-in-a-lifetime shot to join the pros and play roarball – a
high-intensity, co-ed, full-contact sport dominated by the fastest, fiercest animals in the world.
Will's new teammates aren't thrilled about having a little goat on their roster, but Will is
determined to revolutionize the sport and prove once and for all that 'smalls can ball'!
He has to do something he has never done before.
Will Harris (voice), played by Caleb McLaughlin.
Jett Fillmore  (voice), played by Gabrielle Union.
Florence Everson  (voice), played by Jenifer Lewis.
Archie Everhardt  (voice), played by David Harbour.
Modo Olachenko  (voice), played by Nick Kroll.
Olivia Burke  (voice), played by Nicola Coughlan.
Goat is an upcoming American animated sports comedy film directed by Tyree Dillihay from a screenplay
by Aaron Buchsbaum and Teddy Riley and story by Nicolas Curcio and Peter Chiarelli.
The film stars Caleb McLaughlin, alongside an ensemble voice cast including Gabrielle Union, Stephen Curry (who is also producer on the film), Nicola Coughlan, Nick
Kroll, David Harbour, Jenifer Lewis, Aaron Pierre, Patton Oswalt, Andrew Santino, Bobby Lee, Eduardo Franco, Sherry Cola, Jelly Roll and Jennifer Hudson.
It follows an anthropomorphic goat named Will Harris who aspires to become the
greatest of all time at a basketball-like sport known as roarball.
The film was being developed by 2019 and announced in May 2024,
with most of the cast being announced in June 2025.
It is scheduled to be released in the United States on
February 13, 2026, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film explores themes of underdog, friendship,
bullying, challenge, basketball.
The tone is lighthearted and uplifting.